uploaded.tv 2010-03-15

# Uploaded TV Privacy Policy

This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by **Uploaded. B.V.** or it’s subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, Uploaded.TV "services"). In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post separate privacy notices and terms of service to describe how particular services process information.

Protecting the privacy of all of our users ("Users", "you" or "your") is a dedicated commitment of **Uploaded.TV** and all of the services brought to you by Uploaded.TV (collectively, "Uploaded.TV", "us" or "we"). This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy"), applies to all URLs and services provided under the Uploaded.TV name and in connection with the Uploaded.TV marks. It explains how Uploaded.TV treats personal information that we collect and receive on the Uploaded.TV website from our users and visitors.  
  
Personal information  
  
Personal information is information about you that is not otherwise available to the public. As the words imply, this information personally identifies you. Personal information may include, but is not limited to, your name, location, e-mail address, birth date, or other identifying information.

You should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to the Uploaded.TV website, the **Uploaded.TV** URLs, and the services and features provided by **Uploaded.TV**. This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites that you visit before or after us, to the other third party services featured on the **Uploaded.TV** site, or to third party advertisers or affiliates (collectively, "Third Party Services"). Please be sure to familiarize yourself with all of these Third Party Services' privacy policies. For your convenience ONLY, we have listed links to third party privacy policies for some of the parties that we do business with. However, not all Third Party Services may be listed.

**Uploaded TV** is intended for users age 13 or older. **Uploaded TV's** registration process is intentionally designed for such an audience and we will not knowingly collect any information from children under 13. Because of this age limit, this privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of **Uploaded TV**. If you are a parent or become aware of a child registered under the age of 13 please notify **Uploaded TV** 's Policy Manager as provided at the end of this policy.

**Now that you know what this Privacy Policy covers, you may have the following questions:**  
  
What information does Uploaded.TV collect?  
  
For certain services, such as our affiliate programs, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other **Uploaded.TV** services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.

**General User Registration:** When you register to become a member of Uploaded.TV, we collect certain information about you. This information is your desired username, e-mail address, country, zip code, gender and birth date (collectively, "General Membership Information"). In addition, from time to time, we may collect survey responses or other information regarding our users' interests and preferences. However, you will always have the opportunity to opt out from participating in these surveys.  
  
Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
  
**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** Uploaded.TV also collects non-personally identifiable information about you. Currently, upon registration and video upload, **Uploaded.TV** only collects your IP address, which cannot personally identify you. **Uploaded.TV** also compiles user data in the aggregate for purposes of demographic compilations and other data that can help us enhance our user's experience.  
  
Personally Identifiable Information  
  
**Personally Identifiable  Information:** For certain services, such as our advertising programs, we also request credit card or other payment account information which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other **Uploaded.TV** services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.  
  
Community Features  
  
**Community Features:** Once you register for **Uploaded.TV** , you will also have a chance to share other information about yourself. This information will be included in your personal Uploaded.TV public profile and is meant for sharing with other community members of **Uploaded.TV**. We will use your email address in connection with notifications regarding your particular profile; however, you will always have the ability to change and edit this information.  
  
Contests/Sweepstakes  
  
**Contests / Sweepstakes:** We have many contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that may appear on **Uploaded.TV** and may be sponsored by other companies or people. We encourage you to read the Terms of Service of each profile prior to participating in a contest or Uploading 2 TV. These companies may seek to collect personal information from you in order to obtain entry. You can avoid providing your personal information to these companies and sponsors by not participating in these contests, sweepstakes or promotions. Uploaded.TV will endeavour to conspicuously distinguish **Uploaded.TV** sponsored contests and sweepstakes from that of any third party sponsored contest or sweepstakes.  
  
What is collecting all of the above information?  
  
**Cookies:** At Uploaded.TV, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Uploaded.TV features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. So we don't advice to disable or delete cookies, just eat them!

Also, affiliates and advertisers, product and service providers may also use their own cookies when you interact with their sites via Uploaded.TV. You should be aware of this and always consult with their privacy policies.  
  
How do we use membership information and non-personally identifiable information?  
  
**Membership Information:** Uploaded.TV will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information about you to other people or non-affiliated companies except to enable the provision of services or products you have requested or when we have your permission to do so. In some cases your personal information will be given away and or sold through some of our TV shows.

Your e-mail address may be used by us for communications related to the **Uploaded.TV** services, including but not limited to, sending notices about new features, products, or other information of interest to you. Again, you can always opt out of receiving these notices.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** Our advertisers and affiliates may be provided general information or data regarding member usage patterns or interests, or other general demographic information so that they can better serve your needs and preferences. However, such disclosure will not include individually identifiable information.  
  
When will we share or disclose membership information?  
  
Despite our commitment to protecting your privacy, in certain circumstances, **Uploaded.TV** may disclose your membership information under the following circumstances:

(a) **If required to do so by law**

(b) **Pursuant to a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:**

  1. Enforce the Uploaded.TV Terms of Service.
  2. Respond to claims that any uploaded materials violate the rights of third-parties.
  3. Respond to your customer service requests.
  4. Comply with legal process. and/or
  5. Protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Uploaded.TV, its users, or the public.

Since we here at **Uploaded.TV** give you the chance of a life time and allow you to be on TV, we take certain measures to safe guard this privilege by keeping personal and identifying information about you on file. In most cases you must pay to be on TV therefore your credit card information and personal info is on file. In some cases we must keep your personal information, like address, phone number, credit card and bank details on file because we take being on TV very seriously and the governing bodies that regulate TV do as well. Our reasons for keeping your data on file are simple. We give you an opportunity of a life time, if you abuse this privilege by doing illegal acts, we know exactly who you are and where you live.

In the case of extreme violation of the law we will turn over this information to the proper authorities. We have a "be cool" philosophy, simply respect our service and the opportunity we provide you to get your-self produced videos on TV and we will respect your privacy. We will keep all of your personal details private and confidential unless it is determined that you have broken the law or violated our Terms of Service. If you have a problem with this please do not use our service.  
  
How do I edit my membership information?  
  
All of your General Membership Information is located in your personal **Uploaded.TV** profile account. Your profile can be edited at any time, by logging in with your username and password to your profile, then clicking on the "Edit Info" link.  
  
How does uploaded.tv protect my information (security)  
  
Your personal account is protected by your password, which you select. **Uploaded.TV** uses commercially reasonable efforts to protect our user data and restricts our employees access to such data, except to those who's primary job function it is to maintain this data. Please note that apart from the commercially reasonable efforts we employ, due to conditions beyond our control, we cannot guarantee 100% security of user personal data.  
  
What about safety for children?  
  
Again, we at **Uploaded.TV** take the online safety of children very seriously. We do our best not to allow children under the age of 13 to obtain an account. People ages 18 and below should seek the assistance of a parent or guardian when registering and participating on **Uploaded.TV**.  
  
I am an international user, what about my privacy?  
  
**Uploaded.TV** is owned and operated in the Netherlands and our main servers are located in the Netherlands. In certain circumstances master license holders may run additional servers locally in another country. Therefore, the collection of user data is governed, to the extent they exist, by Netherlands and European Union privacy law.  
  
What if uploaded.tv makes changes to this privacy policy?  
  
**Uploaded.TV** may periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will attempt, at our sole discretion, to notify our users of any updates to this Privacy Policy via email. However, we encourage you to periodically revisit the Privacy Policy link on the Uploaded.TV homepage to ensure that you are familiar with the current version. You are responsible for reviewing any revisions to this Privacy Policy, and your continued use of the **Uploaded.TV** website and services after any change to the policy constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy.  
  
What happens when uploaded.tv is sold?  
  
In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that **Uploaded TV** is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.  
  
Note to parents  
  
We want to protect your children. We do our best to keep **Uploaded.TV** safe for people of all ages. If your child is **under 18** and has become a **Uploaded TV** member using a false age, please notify the help desk who will immediately close the account and nullify all personally identifiable information provided by them. If your child is under the age of 18 and you would like to know more about our site, information practices, stored information on your child, or how to close your child's account, contact Uploaded TV: [contact@uploaded.tv](mailto:contact@uploaded.tv).  
  
Can I contact uploaded.tv about my privacy concerns and/or questions?  
  
YES! If you have a privacy concern regarding the Uploaded.TV website or this Privacy Policy feel free to write us at: [contact@uploaded.tv](mailto:contact@uploaded.tv)

**Alternatively, we can be reached at our postal mail address:**

**Attention:**  
Privacy Officer  
c/o Uploaded.TV  
Arendstraat 27  
1223 RE Hilversum    
The Netherlands
